Guide to the Josef Silverstein papers, [ca. 1950-1990]
Silverstein, Josef papers, [ca. 1950-1990]
- Series II. Newspaper Clippings
  - News, 2008, Jan. (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - News, 2008, Apr. (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - News (1 of 2), 2008, May (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - News (2 of 2), 2008, May (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - News, 2008, Jun. (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - News, 2008, Jul. (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - News, 2008, Aug. (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - News, 2008, Sep. (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - News/Notes for Research (1 of 3), 2008 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - News/Notes for Research (1 of 3), 2008 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - News/Notes for Research (1 of 3), 2008 (Box 43, Folder 14)